americaloveshorsepower.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy – America Loves Horsepower

Americaloveshorsepower.com (“americaloveshorsepower.com”, “america loves horsepower”, “our”, “us” or “we”) provides this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information we receive from users of americaloveshorsepower.com and any corresponding applications for mobile devices (collectively, the “Website”). We also want to inform you about your choices regarding information. By visiting the Website, submitting information, or using any of our products or services, you acknowledge that you accept the policies and procedures outlined in this Privacy Policy.  
As used in this Privacy Policy, the terms “using” and “processing” information include using cookies on a computer, subjecting the information to statistical or other analysis and using or handling information in any way, including, but not limited to collecting, storing, evaluating, modifying, deleting, using, combining, disclosing and transferring information within our organization or among affiliates within the United States or internationally.  
This Privacy Policy applies only to information that you provide to us through the Website. Unless otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms of Service, accessible at americaloveshorsepower.com/terms.

### Personally-Identifying Information

Some visitors to the Website interact in ways that provide Personally-Identifying Information (“Personal Information”). This refers to information about you that can be used to contact or identify you, including but not limited to your name, username, pictures, biography, location, website address, email address, phone number, credit card and other billing information and shipping information. The amount and type of Personal Information that we gather depends on the nature of the interaction. You can always refuse to supply Personal Information, with the caveat that it may prevent you from engaging in certain Website features.

### Non-Personally-Identifying Information

We collect Non-Personally-Identifying Information of the sort that web browsers and servers often make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, pages of our Website that you visit, the time spent on those pages, information you search for on our Website, access times and dates, and the date and time of each visitor request. We may also collect Non- Personally-Identifying Information you supply to us regarding your personal preferences and interests, including but not limited to your age, sex, and your friends’ names and email addresses.

### Social Networking Sites

If enabled, you can register to join the Website by logging into your Account with certain third party Social Networking Sites (hereinafter, “SNS”) (including but not limited to Facebook and Twitter) via our Website. If you decide to create your Account by logging into a SNS via the Website, we may extract the Personal Information and Non-Personally-Identifying Information you have provided to the SNS (such as your “real” name, email address and other information you make available via the SNS) from the account you have with such SNS; the information we extract may depend on the privacy settings you have with the SNS.  
We may share the information in your account (including your Personal Information) with the SNSs that you have linked to your account. These third parties have access to your Personal Information only for this purpose (unless the SNS has received your Personal Information independently of the Website).  
We allow users to automatically post recent activity back to Facebook, Twitter and other social sharing websites. You may be able to edit your privacy settings for the content that you post which appears on Facebook and Twitter by making selections in your “Edit Profile” settings via Facebook and Twitter.

### Creating and Administering Accounts

We use your Personally-Identifying Information, and sometimes in conjunction with Non-Personally-Identifying Information, (collectively, “Your Information”), among other things, to create your Account, administer your inquiries, and complete your transactions.  
Public Information  
When you register through the Website and submit your information to create a profile or username, others may see your name. If you choose to provide additional information in your profile, this information will become publicly viewable and others may see your information, including, but not limited to, your photo, location, likes, website and biography. Providing additional information is voluntary and should correlate with the degree of interaction you want to have with the Website. We recommend that you guard your sensitive information.

### Compliance With Laws

We may disclose Your Information in response to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including, but not limited to, subpoenas, court orders or other governmental requests), or when we believe in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of americaloveshorsepower.com, third parties or the public at large, or to prevent or stop activity we may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, illegal, unethical or legally actionable activity.

### Security

We may make any legally required disclosures of any breach of the security, confidentiality, or integrity of your unencrypted electronically stored “personal data” (as defined in applicable state statutes on security breach notification) to you via email or conspicuous posting on this website in the most expedient time possible and without unreasonable delay, insofar as consistent with (i) the legitimate needs of law enforcement or (ii) any measures necessary to determine the scope of the breach and restore the reasonable integrity of the data system.

### Cookies

Like many websites, our Website uses “cookies” to collect information. A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. We use cookies to help us identify and track visitors, their usage of the Website, and their website access preferences. Visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using the Website, with the drawback that certain features of the Website may not function properly without the aid of cookies.  
Third party advertisers on the Website may also place or read cookies on your browser. You can instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit, with the drawback that certain features of the Website may not function properly without the aid of cookies.  
Ads appearing on the Website may be delivered to users by advertising partners who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. Note that this Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by americaloveshorsepower.com on the Website and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### DoubleClick DART Cookies

We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx  
You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.  
You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices.  
Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

### Business Transfers

If we, or substantially all of our assets, were acquired, or in the event of a merger, acquisition or reorganization, or if we go out of business or enter bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Sweet Ride Man may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

### Service Providers

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate the Website, to provide the Website on our behalf, to perform Website-related services (e.g., without limitation, maintenance services, database management, web analytics and improvement of the Website’s features) or to assist us in analyzing how our Website is used.

### International Transfer

Your information may be transferred to and stored on computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

### Links to Other Sites

The Website may contain links to other websites. If you choose to visit an advertiser by “clicking on” a banner ad or other type of advertisement, or click on another third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s website. The fact that we link to a website or present a banner ad or other type of advertisement is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party, nor is it an endorsement of their privacy or information security policies or practices. We do not exercise control over third party websites. These other websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. Other sites follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the Personal Information you submit to them. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites you visit.  
As stated in our Terms of Service, we have not reviewed, and cannot review, all of the material, including computer software, made available through the websites and webpages to which americaloveshorsepower.com links and that link to americaloveshorsepower.com. Sweet Ride Man does not have any control over third party websites and webpages. You are responsible for taking precautions as necessary to protect yourself and your computer systems from viruses, worms, Trojan horses, and other harmful or destructive content. Sweet Ride Man disclaims any responsibility for any harm resulting from your use of any third party website or webpage.

### Children Under the Age of 13

Any use or access to the Website by anyone under the age of 13 is strictly prohibited. We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that their child has provided us with Personal Information without their consent, he or she should contact us at americaloveshp(at)gmail(.com). If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete such information from our files.

### Use of Information In The Aggregate

We may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to the Website, and may release Your Information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of the Website. We may display this information publicly or provide it to others.  
We may share aggregated information with third parties to provide you with a better experience, to improve the quality and value of the Website, to analyze and understand how our Website is used, for industry analysis, and demographic profiling. We may also use the combined information without aggregating it to serve you specifically, for instance to deliver a product to you according to your preferences or restrictions.

### Email Communications

We may use your Personal Information to contact you with Website newsletters, marketing or promotional materials, to tell you about new Website features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with the Website and other information that may be of interest to you. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications.

### Changing or Deleting Your Information

Members may review, update, correct or delete the Personal Information in their account by editing such information via the Website. We may retain an archived copy of your records as required by law or for legitimate business purposes.

### Privacy Policy Changes

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time, and in our sole discretion. We encourage visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to our Privacy Policy.

### Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at americaloveshp[at]gmail[dot]com
